Guide to the Charles DeWitt Watts Papers, 1917-2004 and undated RL.01352
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Professional Files Series, 1945-2003 and undated, 12 boxes
  - Other Professional Files
    - Birchett, Mark G., undated (Box 16)
    - Capital Health Systems Agency, 1974-1979, 5 of 7 folders (Box 16)
    - Capital Health Systems Agency, 1974-1979, 2 of 7 folders (Box 17)
    - Carr Agyapong, D., 1995 (Box 17)
    - Citron, David S., 1980 (Box 17)
    - CVs, 1977-1993 (Box 17)
    - Drew, Charles (Dr.): speeches, events, research, articles, 1945-2001, 6 folders (Box 17)
    - Drew, Charles (Dr.): Watts oral history transcript for American Red Cross project, 2001-2002 (Box 17)
    - Drug Enforcement Administration registration, 1981-1992 (Box 17)
    - Duke University Medical Center, 1976-1984, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Durham Ambulatory Surgical Center, 1984-1993, 5 folders (Box 18)
    - Malpractice suit, 1973-1974 (Box 18)
    - Medical Associates, Inc., 1964, 1986-1987, 2000, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - North Carolina hospital discharge data, 2000 June (Box 18)
    - Notes, lectures, and articles on surgical procedures, 1953-1994, 8 of 20 folders (Box 18)
    - Notes, lectures, and articles on surgical procedures, 1953-1994, 12 of 20 folders (Box 19)
    - Residency records, 1945-1949 (Box 19)
    - Spellman, Mitchell (Dr.), 1970-1974 (Box 19)
    - Stead, Eugene Jr. (Dr.), 1999 (Box 19)
    - Swift, LeRoy, 1982 (Box 19)
- Medical Records Series, 1945-1980, 6 folders
  Contains medical records with personally-identifiable information separated from the rest of the collection. Of particular note is a record of surgeries performed by Dr. Watts, beginning with his residency in 1945. Folders reflect the title of the parallel folder in the main collection from which the records were pulled.
  Conditions Governing Access note
  [Medical records are currently closed to use. Please contact Research Services for information regarding access to these materials.]
  - Surgical record, 1945-1968 (Box 20)
  - Surgical record for American College of Surgeons, 1954 (Box 20)
  - Lincoln Hospital staff, 1960-1964 (Box 20)
  - Lincoln Hospital correspondence and reports, 1960-1968 (Box 20)
  - Eosinophilic gastroenteritis, 1978 (Box 20)
  - Diverticular disease, 1980 (Box 20)
- Accession 2005-0050
  Oversize Material
  - Miscellaneous (Oversize-folder 1)